翻译: Amber  宛若安宁  猫  Jamie
嗨 親愛的
Hey, honey.
你在干嘛
Whatcha doing?
校对: 皮皮
看你的信用卡賬單
Just going through your credit card bills.
呃 來了
Uh, ye... Coming!
后期: Danica
家里沒別的人 Molly
Nobody else is home, Molly.
你坐下
Have a seat.
压制: 凯撒
這簡直像你的月事
This is becoming, like, an every month thing for you.
現在我們就一個經濟來源
Well, now that we're a one-income family
真的得節省點了
we really have got to watch our spending.
我最近一直很節約啊
Hey, I've been really good lately...
不去星巴克了 不做指甲了
no Starbucks, no manicures,
- 只去看了一次手相  - 什么
- I've only had one palm reading. - What?
看 Olga夫人說了你會生氣的
See? Madam Olga said you'd be upset.
你真好笑
You're hilarious.
我剛把這些賬單過了一遍
Look, I was going over these bills,
我認為有些地方的錢
and I think there's a few more areas
完全可以省下來
where we can cut back.
- 說來聽聽  - 比如這個
- Let's hear it. - Well, how about this
"上蠟 脫蠟"處 是洗車嗎
"Wax On, Wax Off" Place, is that a car wash?
這完全可以在自家車道上搞定
'Cause I could do that in the driveway.
是我的比基尼蜜蠟 你想在車道上搞定嗎
That's my bikini wax, you want to do that in the driveway?
我們把這個歸到"醫療開支"里
We'll file that under "Medical expenses"
還有我們不需要的 NFL付費運動節目包
Here's what we don't need... NFL Sports Package.
不不不不
No, no, no, no!
這對我們都有好處的
We both need that.
我要是不在這看橄欖球
If I'm not watching football here,
就會去酒吧里看
I'm at a bar.
如果我進了酒吧 就會喝啤酒
If I'm at a bar, having a few beers.
現在比賽是在周日 周一和周四
Now, games are Sunday, Monday, and Thursday.
就算每場比賽至少三瓶酒
Let's say at least three beers per game,
乘上十七個禮拜
times 17 weeks.
加上季后賽
plus playoffs.
為了省50塊錢
Saving $50 has cost you...
換來一個酗酒的丈夫
one husband to alcoholism.
什么都比這好
Anything's better than this.
- 什么  - 什么
- What? - What?
好吧
O-Okay.
這就有一個
Oh, here, here's a perfect example
我們不需要的奢侈品
of a luxury item we do not need.
桶裝水
Bottled water.
Mike 不喝水會死的
Mike, we need water to live.
我們有水
We have it...
就在這
right here.
看 還是免費的
Look, and it's free.
從密歇根湖直接運過來
From Lake Michigan to our home.
簡直是絕世好水
See? Perfectly good water.
你是要喝還是要用來漆房子啊
You gonna drink that or paint the house with it?
等等 讓這里面的礦物質
Well, give it a second, you just got to let the minerals
和維他命沉淀一下
and vitamins sink to the bottom.
或者 我還有個主意 你喝那個
Or... I have another idea... how about you drink that,
我喝罐裝水
I'll drink the bottled water.
一個人喝能喝更久
It'll last twice as long.
看誰給我們省了一半的水錢
Who just cut our water bill in half?
不用謝
You're welcome.
沒水了
Out of water?
我還有的是呢
Mine's still full.
我也馬上就有了 讓我換桶水
Mine will be... let me just swap out this dead soldier.
你舉不起那桶水的 我來幫你
You can't lift that jug, let me help you with it.
我可以的 這是我的水
No, I got it, it's my water.
我能換的
I can change it.
你就享受肝炎陰影的籠罩吧
Just enjoy your "Cloudy with a Chance of Hep C"
需要幫忙嗎
Would you like some help?
我能搞定
No, I got it.
噢
Oh...
天哪
God...!
小菜一碟
Easy-peasy.
好了 現在就需要
All right, so it's just a little...
把它翻一面了 開始
a full flip, and there we go.
好喝極了
It's delicious.
迈克和茉莉
第四季 第六集
电波诚译
把整壺都留下吧 我昨晚幾乎沒睡
Just leave the pot. I hardly slept.
你應該弄個人形抱枕
Well, you should get a body pillow.
自從我有了之后 每天都睡得像嬰兒一樣
Ever since I got one, I've been sleeping like a baby.
我真的醒來后發現大拇指在嘴巴里
I literally woke up with my thumb in my mouth.
別告訴我你另一個拇指在哪
Well, don't tell me where the other thumb was,
我昨晚的噩夢夠多了
I had enough nightmares last night.
你聽過那個
Have you heard the one where you wake
被室友搞人形抱枕時發出的激情聲音
to the passionate sounds of your roommate
吵醒的噩夢嗎
humping a body pillow?
我說過了 我只是把抱枕翻到涼的那一面而已
I told you, I was just flipping it to the cool side.
我的大腿太熱了
My thighs get hot.
不 在夢里首先我所有牙齒都碎了
No, this dream started with all my teeth crumbling.
這通常表示著無能為力
Oh, that usually represents a feeling of powerlessness,
比如你的生活開始分崩離析
like your life is falling apart.
或者也可以反映你的口腔衛生情況
Or it could reflect your dental hygiene.
用停車罰單剔牙
Picking your teeth with a parking citation
和用牙線是不一樣的
is not the same as flossing.
我的牙掉光之后 我一下子到了廁所
After my teeth fell out, I was suddenly in a bathroom.
坐在馬桶上 錢就開始從那里涌出來
I sat on a pot, and money just started pouring out of it...
硬幣啦 鈔票啦 什么都有
coins, bills, everything.
我想要去撿的時候 它們就全被沖掉了
But when I tried to grab it, it all flushed away.
拉錢出來
Diarrhea money.
這種夢很常見
This is a very common dream.
腹瀉表示你對生活缺乏控制
Your loose bowels represent a lack of control in your life.
錢可以代表任何東西
The money could be anything.
比如錢
Like money.
沒錯 就是錢
Yeah! Money!
按照我和Molly還款的速度
At the rate me and Molly are paying down our debt,
我們的第一個家很可能就是養老院了
our first home's gonna be a nursing home.
呵呵
Boo-hoo.
我的信用等級糟透了 我根本就不能欠債
My credit rating is so bad, I can't even get into debt.
嗯
Mm!
贊美主 希望那天早日來臨吧
Praise God, someday.
真為你們難過
Yeah, I feel bad for you guys,
跟我奶奶生活了三十七年之后
'cause after 37 years of living with my grandma
我可有錢了
I'm flush.
這頓我買單 是吧
I'm paying for lunch, aren't I?
Samuel 拿甜點菜單來
Samuel, get me the dessert menu.
哦 糟了 哎
Oh, uh-oh... Ooh...
想進去看看嗎
Do you want to go in?
不 不 不 我在這兒挺好
No, no, no, I'm fine out here.
我答應Mike要好好表現了
I promised Mike I would be good,
我會乖乖的
and I'm going to be good.
天啊 這些鞋子太美了
God, those shoes are beautiful.
我都能透過玻璃聞到那皮革的味道
Oh, I think I can smell the leather through the glass.
你不去試試嗎
Can't you just try them on?
不 我不試
No, I can't try them on.
一穿上它們 我就
I try them on, I'm...
我就得買了 我說
I'm gonna buy 'em, and, I mean...
我覺得如果我試了
You know, I guess if I tried on just one...
號碼有點小
you know, in maybe, like, a size too small,
就會夾腳 這個試鞋體驗
then it would pinch, and that would be a really
可不好 我可不想
bad shoe experience, and I wouldn't want to...
我可不想買它們
I wouldn't want to get them, you know.
但 但是 如果它偏大 穿起來合適
B-But, if-if they run big, and it fits perfectly,
那我就 那就是命運啊
then I got, you know, that's fate...
我哪兒能跟命運抗爭啊 我肯定得買啊
and who am I to deal with fate, so then I am buying the shoe...
不 跟你說 我還是就
No, you know what, I'm-I'm just gonna st...
我就不進去了
I'm not going in.
好吧 咱走吧
Okay, then we'll leave.
不 怎么能走呢
No, we're not leaving.
你得穿上試試 進去
You're trying on shoes! Get in there!
嘿 嘿 嘿 嘿
Hey, hey, hey, hey!
不要看靴子 不 來這邊
We don't need boots. No, come here.
就是那個寶貝兒 那個黑色的
These are the showstoppers. The black ones.
喂 這些都是黑的啊
Yeah, they're all black.
不是那個丑黑
Yeah, not the ugly black ones,
是那個好看的黑 那個
the amazing black ones. These.
趕緊的 不 不是
Come on. No... no!
我可不是KISS的貝斯手
I'm not the bass player for KISS.
KISS 美國重金屬搖滾樂隊
快點 上面的
Come on, one up,
上面的 再邊上第二個
one up, and two over.
上面一層 上 上 上
One up, up, up, up.
邊上第二個 第二個
Two over. Two over.
第二 對了
Two... yes.
對 對 對了
Yes, yes, yes.
真漂亮
These are nice.
對吧 我就知道 可不是啊
Right? I know! Hello!
請問這個鞋有沒有九號的
Excuse me, do you have these in nine?
或是八號的 八號
Or eight? Eight?
但我穿九號啊
But I'm a nine.
好吧 好吧 號是不是偏小啊
All right, fine. Do they run small?
這是最后一雙了 是八號的
That's the last pair we have and it's an eight.
你說八號 那我要了
Did you say eight? 'Cause I'll take 'em.
我以為你不會買的
I thought you weren't gonna buy anything.
我不 但你要買 刷我的信用卡
I'm not, you are. Put it on my credit cards.
我從沒來過這兒 我在巷子里等你
I was never here. I'll meet you in the alley.
天啊
Oh, God.
你怎么讓我使喚你做一些
Why did you let me let you do something
我不應該做的事兒啊
that I wasn't supposed to do?
你怎么能這么美啊
And why are you so beautiful?
我知道這話從你這個嗑藥妹妹口中說出來很怪
I know this is weird, coming from your stoner sister:
但你真的有問題了
But you've got a problem.
她唯一能有的問題就是
The only problem
如果Mike看到這雙鞋了
she'll have is if Mike sees them.
我幫你把它們放到我振動棒的柜子里吧
You want me to keep them in my vibrator cabinet?
我像藏槍一樣鎖著它們
I lock those up like guns.
不用 既然我都買了 我就得誠實
No. I mean, I did it, I have to be honest
承認我的錯誤
and own up to my own mistakes.
Molly
Molly!
老天 脫下來 脫下來 快脫下來
Oh, God, get 'em off, get 'em off, get 'em off!
嗨 好啊 你
Hey. Hey. Hey, you.
我整天都在家
I stayed home all day,
我可不知道她倆都干嘛了
I don't know what these two did.
她倆怎么了
What's up with those two?
喝醉了 嗑藥了 誰知道啊
Drunk? High? Who knows.
上癮是個問題 我們得理解
Addiction is a problem, and we have to be understanding.
你怎么這么高
Why are you so tall?
你怎么這么帥
Why are you so handsome?
- 你去哪兒  - 你要去哪兒
- Where are you going? - Where are you going?
你干嘛呢
What are you doing?
- 不要啊  - 那是新鞋嗎
- No, no. - Are those new shoes?
- 不是  - 真的嗎
- No. - Really?
不是
No.
- 多少錢買的  - 促銷價
- How much were they? - They were on sale.
- 真的嗎  - 是啊
- Really? - Yes.
Molly
Molly?
- 不是  - 你殺了我算了
- No. - You are killing me!
行了 不就是一雙鞋嗎
Come on, they're one pair of shoes.
我保證再也不買了
I promise I won't do it again.
你每次都這么說
You say that every time.
但現在我們債務纏身 都壓在我肩上了
But we're drowning in debt and it's all on my shoulders.
沒都在你肩上啊 我肩上也扛著呢
It's not all on your shoulders, it's on my shoulders, too.
拿什么扛啊
How?
你每天都上班嗎
Are you going to work every day?
不 你只會出去買東西
No, you're just going out and shopping
花光我所有的錢
and spending all of my money.
你說什么
Really?
慘了
Oh, boy.
你的錢 哇
Your money? Wow.
我 別反過來怪我
Look, I... don't turn this on me,
是你非要買什么蠢鞋的
you're the one who bought the stupid shoes.
知道了 蠢鞋 你的錢
Got it. Stupid shoes, your money.
在你亂花錢這件事上
Hey, I'm right on this one,
我是對的 別想讓我內疚
and you're not making me feel bad about it.
該死 我好內疚
Damn it! I feel bad about it.
Vince
Vince.
來啦 坐吧 冠軍
There he is. Have a seat, champ.
我煮了一壺咖啡 給你煎了蛋
Brewed a fresh pot of coffee and made you some eggs.
你干嘛給我做早餐
Why are you making me breakfast?
你肯定餓了
You got to be hungry
跟你媳婦大喊大叫了這一通
after that ass chewing you gave your wife.
你聽見了
You heard about that?
整個屋子都快震塌了
The whole house is a buzz.
坐下吧 大英雄
Sit down, hero.
大英雄
Hero.
我昨晚在地下室的沙發上睡的
I slept on a La-Z-Boy in the basement last night.
耶穌還戴著荊棘冠冕呢
And Jesus wore a crown of thorns.
只是一場關于買鞋的爭執罷了
It was just a dumb fight about shoes.
不 遠遠不只是那個
No, it was much more than that.
你說了 "我的錢"
You said, "My money."
你有種啊 說出了
You had the balls to say
自聯合賬戶存在以來
what a generation of men have wanted to
一代男人想說而不敢說的話
since the dawn of joint checking accounts.
早上好
Morning.
早上好 Moll
Morning, Moll.
- 鞋子真漂亮  - 你來咬我呀
-Nice shoes. -Yeah, bite me.
就是告訴你一聲
Just so you know,
我今天就去找工作
I'm going out and getting a job today,
這樣就能把你的寶貝錢都還給你
just so I can pay you back your precious money.
Molly 別荒唐了 你不用去找工作
Molly, you're being ridiculous. You don't have to get a job.
現在我還荒唐了
Oh, am I ridiculous now, too?
行 我這就把荒唐當成我的特殊技能
You know what? I'm gonna put that on my resume
寫進我的簡歷里
under "Special Skills""
對了 你要是
Hey, if you're
想找工作 我有個哥們開了個學校
looking for a job, I got a buddy who owns a school
專門教外國人開車
teaching foreigners how to drive cars.
你都不知道這有多掙錢
You'd be surprised how much money you can make
非法移民市場可大了去了
exploiting the undocumented immigrant market.
我好歹是個碩士 Vince
I have a master's degree, Vince, okay?
我覺得我不至于去干那個吧
I think I can get something a little bit better than that.
哇
Wow.
跟你的性福說拜拜吧
You may never get laid again.
你有什么技能嗎
So, do you have any skills?
有 我曾是有編制的芝加哥教師
Uh, yeah, I was a teacher for the Chicago school system
過去十年里一直是
for the last ten years, so...
那就是沒有技能了
Oh. No skills.
不 不 我有技能呢 我能打字
No, no, no, I have, I have skills... I can type.
我能熟練使用電腦
I'm very good with computer.
很不錯呀
Oh, that's terrific.
你覺得粉刷匠怎么樣
Uh, how do you feel about house painting?
粉刷匠
Painting.
當然了 我不可能一開始就讓你做粉刷工作
Well, I couldn't start you off as a painter.
也許先刮大白 或當小工
No, maybe a scraper or a prepper.
搖勻油漆罐子
A can... shaker. That...
我 我是個碩士
I-I have a master's degree.
要是你的專業是
Well, if it's a master's degree in...
空調維修 那我們正需要這種人才
air-conditioning repair, you're in luck.
不是的 我的專業是中世紀文學
Uh, no, it's in medieval literature.
我 我只是覺得
Um, I just, I just think that I have
除了體力活 我還可以做些別的工作回饋社會
a little more to offer the world than manual labor.
現在的社會才懶得管你呢
Well, the world doesn't give a hot crap.
你想不想聽我說句大實話
Do you mind if, uh, we get real for a second?
比剛才那句還實在嗎
Realer than that?
聽我說
Here it is
我們都完了
We're all screwed.
要是你現在沒錢 你永遠也富不了
If you don't have money now, you are never getting any.
因為有錢的那仨
Because the three guys that have it all
可不會把錢白分給你
are not sharing.
我是來找工作的
Are you sure that you're the one
是不是問錯負責人了
I'm supposed to be talking to about getting a job?
這兒沒工作 實話告訴你吧
There are no jobs. In fact,
這家中介公司兩周內就要倒了
this agency is shutting down in two weeks.
我們全都要失業了
We're all getting laid off.
我剛剛買了一輛裝備齊全的福特福克斯
And I just got a fully-loaded Ford Focus.
很不錯嘛
Those are nice.
是嗎
Yeah.
能當房子住嗎
Nice enough to live in?
話說起來 我 我該
You know what, I'm just...
我該走了
I'm probably just gonna go.
對了 這個給你
Hey, you know... how about you...
午飯的時候加個菜吧
get yourself a little treat at lunch,
我請客
on me.
老天保佑你
Bless you.
你知道我只會去拿這去買酒
You know I'm gonna spend this on liquor.
我了解
I do.
真沒想到我淪落至此
Can't believe this is the only job I could get.
我是個碩士
I have a master's degree.
我學車就是為了當出租車司機
I'm just doing this so I can get a job driving a taxi.
我還是個博士呢
And I have a PhD.
挺厲害啊你 不會開車的博士
Well, good for you, Dr. Don't Have a Driver's License.
十和二
Ten and two!
那是十一和一 十和二
That's 11 and one! Ten and two!
你知道嗎 這是我和Molly第一次吵得這么兇
You know, this is me and Molly's first big fight.
兩口子哪有不拌嘴的
Well, that's what happens with couples.
我還記得我倆第一次吵架
I remember our first big fight.
你帶口琴來上班那次嗎
The day you brought harmonica to work?
不 再之前那次
No. Before that.
我從你手里搶走了
When I snatched that second double cheeseburger
第二個雙層芝士漢堡
out of your hand.
噢 是啊 那次太糟了
Oh, right, that was a bad one.
是的 你咬了我一口
Yeah. You bit me.
我發現那不是漢堡的時候就松口了
I let up when I realized it wasn't hamburger.
我就是不太了解
I-I just didn't understand
你當時的情況
the issues that you were going through,
可怎么說 我也是因為愛你才那么做的
but you know, I did it out of love.
噢 我記得
Oh, I know.
那之后我就加入暴食者匿名互戒會了
It was right after that that I joined OA.
Molly
Molly?!
她也在那
She was there, too.
改變了我的人生
Changed my whole life.
不 是Molly
No, Molly.
Molly
Molly?
噢 開什么玩笑
Oh, you got to be kidding me.
走啊 走啊
Drive. Drive.
是紅燈呢
It's a red light.
那就 看看左右兩邊 開車 開車
Then... check both ways, but go, go,
快開車
Go!
她這是要去哪呢
Where is she going?
她明明正看著我啊
She was looking right at me.
哇 還沒見過誰這樣氣沖沖地開走一輛普銳斯的
Wow. Never seen somebody storm off in a Prius.
雖然一點噪音都沒有 可有時無聲勝有聲
Didn't make any noise, but it sure made her point.
跟著她
Follow that car.
該死的 甩不掉那兩個傻瓜
Damn it, we can't shake these clowns.
警察在后面 不是應該靠邊停車嗎
Aren't we supposed to pull over for the police?
閃爍燈和警笛都開了時才要
Only if there's lights and a siren.
天啊
Gah! Oh.
我的天吶
Oh, my goodness.
教授 專心開車
Just keep it together, professor,
向左轉
and make a left up here.
別打燈
Don't use your signal,
這樣他們就知道我們往哪邊轉了
they'll know which way we're turning.
轉彎時加速就好了
Just accelerate through the turn.
學著點
Watch it.
真不懂那女人為什么還來學車
I don't know why that woman's taking classes.
看到她剛怎么轉彎的沒
You see the way she just took that corner?
Molly 靠邊停車 我們得談談
Molly, pull over, we need to talk.
警察居然認識你
The police know you?!
你不會是罪犯吧
Are you a criminal?
不 現在我是你的救星
No, I'm your one chance out of this mess.
減速帶
Speed bump.
我不想八卦的
You know, I hate to pry,
可很明顯 這都是因為
but obviously, this is a result
你和你的伴侶
of a lack of communication
缺乏溝通才這樣
between you and your spouse.
你 閉嘴
Shut up, you.
我只是想說 你可以做好的
I'm just saying, I know how you can be.
嘿 這不是我的錯
Hey, I'm not in the wrong, here.
- 是她買了鞋子  - 不
- She bought the shoes. - No.
看你都在干嘛 不但沒去想解決方法
See what you did, there? Instead of trying to find a solution,
還在怪她
you're trying to lay blame.
沒搞錯吧 就算是她做錯了 我也不對
Really? So even when she's wrong I don't get to be right.
奧普拉說過 "婚姻或真理"
Like Oprah says, "Do you want to be right
"你選哪個"
or do you want to be married?"
奧普拉就沒結婚啊
Oprah isn't married.
好吧 但她有Gayle
Well, she's got Gayle.
奧普拉好友 有傳兩人為同性戀伴侶
快點 Molly 快停車
Come on, Molly, pull over the car, please.
求你了 讓我停車吧
Please, please let me pull over.
好吧 你非要這么遵守法律的話
Oh, fine. If you're gonna be such a stickler for the law,
永遠也別指望能在這當上出租車司機了
you're never gonna make it as a cabbie in this town.
我知道她是我老婆
I know she's my wife,
可這還是逃避追捕吧
but this is still evading arrest.
三思而后行
Don't go in with a hot head.
記住 要聆聽 應答
Remember, listen, acknowledge,
接受 道歉
admit, and apologize.
啦
Laaa.
奧普拉說的
Oprah?
我說的
Carl.
你到底在干嘛啊
What the hell are you doing?
我在賺自己的錢啊
I am trying to earn my own money.
- 這太可笑了  - 為什么
- This is ridiculous. - Why?
你說得很對 你賺的錢又不是我的錢
What you said is true... the money you make is not my money.
- 是你的錢  - 不 才不是
- It is your money. - No, it's not.
我整天游手好閑 揮金如土
I'm not working, I'm just spending.
你一天忙到晚 努力想成為一名作家
Well, you're working at trying to be a writer.
我都不知道我能不能行
I don't even know if I'm good enough to be one.
- 你可以的  - 你又怎么知道
- You are. - How do you know?
我自己都不知道 所以每天想這想那
I...I don't even know. And that's what scares the hell out of me.
然后就感到害怕不安 然后我就
Then I get scared, and I get nervous, and I...
去逛街 一去逛街
go shopping, and if I go shopping,
就會買那些蠢鞋 就為了讓自己好受點
I buy stupid shoes, all trying to make me feel better.
那你好受點了嗎
Do they make you feel better?
嗯
Yes.
那你應該留著
Then you should keep 'em.
不 不行
No, I can't.
可以 可以的
Yes, you can.
我希望你開心
I want you to be happy.
因為如果你不開心
'Cause when you're not happy,
我也痛苦不堪
I'm miserable.
那樣的話
In that case, there's a...
要是再有個包和腰帶 我會更開心的
there's a purse and a belt that might put me over the moon.
- 別得寸進尺  - 知道了
- Don't push it. - I know.
你說的對 我打算
You're right. And I'm going to,
我要更加努力工作 變得更好
I'm going to work really hard to be better.
你知道嗎
You know what?
我要把我的信用卡給你
I'm gonna give you my credit cards.
- 你不用這樣  - 我就要這樣
- You don't have to do that. - No, I want-I want to.
我已經取消你的信用卡了
I already canceled them.
我偷偷開的你也取消了嗎
Even the ones you don't know about?
我真是被你吃定了
You're gonna be the death of me.
回家見
I'll see you at home.
對不起
Sorry.
我們有麻煩了嗎
Are we in trouble?
沒事沒事 在下個紅綠燈處轉彎
No, no. Just take a turn at the next light and head
往密歇根大道走
towards Michigan Avenue.
我要把新買的包和腰帶退回去
I've got a purse and a belt I need to return.
我想退掉這些東西 太搞笑了
Okay, I'd like to return these. Uh, funny story...
我回到家后 發現我老公
I got home, and my husband had already
給我買了一樣的鞋子 一樣的腰帶
bought me the same shoes, the same belt
還有一樣的包
and the same purse.
我們真是心有靈犀呢
I mean, does he know me or what?
這鞋都被你穿過了
You wore these.
沒有 沒有
No, no, I didn't.
還是熱的
They're still warm.
好吧 那把包和腰帶退了
All right, then take back the purse and belt.
我的婚姻都命懸一線了
Come on, my frickin' marriage is on the line here.
我最多只能跟你換張折價券
Best I can do is give you a store credit.
好吧 那我還是都不退了吧
Okay, I'll take the purse and the belt.
电波字幕组 欢迎您的加入
官方网站:www.dbfansub.com
新浪微博:@电波字幕组